Peter Le

Adelaide, SA | rthinh2002@gmail.com | (+61) 474-509-786 | LinkedIn | Portfolio

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Experienced Web Developer with a strong background in front-end technologies and JavaScript frameworks such as React and Angular. Adept at translating UI/UX wireframes into functional code and optimizing web applications for speed and scalability. Committed to collaborative problem-solving and keeping up with industry best practices.

EMPLOYMENT

eBottli - Full Stack Developer; Adelaide, South Australia

Jun 2023 – Present

- Successfully contributed to a team of 4 developers in a project that increased customer engagement by 35%.
- Designed and implemented 8+ web application pages using Figma, conforming to UI/UX best practices.
- Translated UI/UX design wireframes into functional front-end code using HTML, CSS, and TypeScript.
- Led the development and deployment of 3 web applications using React.js and Angular.
- Headed code refactoring efforts, reducing maintenance time by 25%.
- Improved rendering speed of 2 existing web applications by 2-3 seconds, increasing performance by 50%.
- Resolved 2+ cross-browser and multi-device compatibility issues, including mobile view and computer view.
- Contributed to 3 technical solution proposals for clients after consulting with stakeholders.

eBottli - Software Engineer Intern; Adelaide, South Australia

Apr 2023 – Jun 2023

- Reduced build and deployment time by 30% by automating key processes.
- Prototyped 3 web interfaces in an agile development environment using JavaScript, TypeScript, and Node.js.
- Enhanced UI/UX designs through 4+ collaborative sessions with designers and front-end developers.
- Designed Firebase database rules that improved data security by 30%.

Bambrick Legal – AI Research Assistant; Kent Town, South Australia

Apr 2023 – Sep 2023

- Worked on AI automation projects to optimize company processes, reducing manual tasks by 25%.
- Integrated AI technologies, like the ChatGPT API, into existing workflows, increasing operational efficiency by 20%.

SKILLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

- Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, Python.
- Frameworks/Tools: React.js, Angular, Node.js, Firebase, MongoDB, AWS, Oracle.
- **Soft skills:** Bilingual, Excellent Verbal and Written Communication, Strong Problem-Solving Abilities, Attention to Detail, Collaborative Teamwork, Up to date with Latest Technologies.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

AI Image Generator Website

Jan 2023 – Feb 2023

 Created a platform for generating and sharing AI-driven art. Utilized JavaScript, Node.js, React.js, MongoDB, and OpenAI API to manage large data sets of up to 10GB.

Team Pursuit Management Website

July 2022 – Nov 2022

• Created a web application to manage Team Pursuit racing strategy and analyze team performance after different matches by generating data and graphs.

Event Planning Website

May 2022 - June 2022

• Built a feature-rich event planning website to support user-generated content. Incorporated features for creating, editing, and deleting events as well as inviting users.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, The University of Adelaide

Sep 2020 – Jul 2023

• Major: Computer Science

• **GPA Achieved:** 5.913/7